investellect.net 2017-11-20

# Investellect - Force Of Experience

Please read the following terms regarding our privacy policy. 

An important part of the relationship we have with our Clients is the information you share with us. We want you to know how we treat your private information. Investellect - Force of Expirience protects our clients' privacy and does its best to provide their safety and convenience online. The Investellect - Force of Expirience website is subject to this "Privacy Policy". It regulates data accumulation and usage at the website. Using the Investellect - Force of Experience website infers your consent to the data practices given in this statement. 

### Your Personal Information Accumulation

Investellect - Force of Experience accumulates such personal data as your name, ewallet information, secret question, secret answer and e-mail address. Some details about your software and hardware which are collected automatically by our platform's website. We receive such information as the type of your browser, your IP address, access times, domain names to maintain high level of our services and to manage the statistics of the Investellect - Force of Experience website. Please consider the fact that if you reveal your personal data directly through the public message boards of the Investellect - Force of Experience website, we are irresponsible for data privacy and such data can be used by third parties. We assure you that we do not read or interfere into your online private communication. Investellect - Force of Experience "Privacy Policy" does not apply to other websites which you can decide to visit using a link from our website. That's why read attentively their privacy statements before giving them the right to collect your personal information. Please be aware that Investellect - Force of Experience does not bear responsibility for the content and rules of other websites. 

### Use of Cookies

So-called "cookies" are used at the Investellect - Force of Experience website to help you in personalizing your online presence. A cookie means a text file which a web-page server places on your hard disk. Cookies pose no threat to your computer: no memory leak, virus infection or other undesirable results can be expected. Only web-server in the domain, which issued it to you, can read it, because cookies are uniquely assigned. 

One of the main purposes of cookies is saving your time, which is very convenient for you. Cookie is intended to signal the web-server that the user has returned to a particular page. For instance if you registered and personalized on the Investellect - Force of Experience's website to use its services, the cookie is necessary for the website to recall some particular information at your following visit. The process of your personal data recording becomes simpler and easier. Such data may include billing addresses, shipping addresses, etc. When you come back to the Investellect - Force of Experience website again, the data you conveyed before can be restored. In this case you get quick access to the necessary Investellect - Force of Experience website features. 

You can accept and decline cookies as you like. Most web browsers allow cookies by default, but usually you have an ability to set your browser to reject cookies if you want to. But if you make up your mind to reject cookies, you may fail to use all the interactive features of our website to the full as well as the features of other websites. 

### Changes to This Statement

Investellect - Force of Experience reserves the right to amend occasionally this "Privacy Policy" to correspond actual company's and customers' interaction. Investellect - Force of Experience strongly recommends you to review this Statement from time to time not to miss the updates. In this case you'll be always aware of Investellect - Force of Experience safety methods towards your personal data. 

### Contact Information

Investellect - Force of Experience is glad to receive your comments concerning this "Privacy Policy". In case you think that Investellect - Force of Experience does not follow the rules and violate this Statement, contact Investellect - Force of Experience at **abuse@investellect.net** We guarantee that we will take commercially reasonable efforts to discover and solve the problem.
